codango.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy - Codango.Net / Codango™

Codango™ will always notify you when it is collecting personally identifiable information about you, as well as the use or uses Codango™ intends to make with such information. For example, we may need to collect information to respond to your listing requests, posting reviews, requesting information, or to allow you to send or post messages, or for billing purposes. We also keep information about customers, and purchases in a secure database on my servers in order to fulfill online transaction and banking requirements.

Anonymous Information

We may collect certain non-personal information from your IP address. This information is used only to provide an enhanced on-line experience for my visitors by optimizing my Web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, IP address, referral data, platform type, and search terms ). We may also use this non-personal information to determine the total number of visitors to my web site.

Use Of Cookies

When you view the Codango™ web site, I may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a ‘Cookie’ and will help me in many ways. For example, Cookies allow me to tailor my web site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

Information Collected In Delivery Of Advertisements

In the course of delivering an advertisement to Codango™ visitors, Codango™, or its advertising agency, does not collect any personally-identifiable information about the Web site user, such as the user’s name, address, phone number or email address. Codango™ advertising processes do, however, collect non-personally identifiable information, such as the server a user’s computer is logged onto, the user’s browser type (for example, Internet Explorer or Chrome), and whether the user responded to the advertisement delivered.

Codango™ use of the non-personally identifiable information collected by Codango™ advertising processes may include targeting advertisements and measuring advertisement effectiveness.

Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information about my visitors is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted by those visitors. Codango™ uses such information only for the purpose for which it was submitted, unless we disclose other uses at the time of collection. Codango™ does not sell personal information to third parties. Codango™ may share personally identifiable information with other parts of my company, but this will never be used on an individual basis outside of the company. Codango™ maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of personally identifiable information in its possession. Codango™ may use such personally identifiable information in the aggregate (non-identifiable) form to make our Web site better and more responsive to the needs of our visitors. This statistical compilation of non-identifiable information may also be used by or provided to others for marketing, advertising, or research purposes.

Links To Other Sites

Codango™ chooses its advertisers and business partners carefully. However, Codango™ is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to or from my web site. These links are meant for the visitor’s convenience only. Links to third party Web sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by Codango™ of content, policies or practices of such sites. Once you have left the Codango™ Web sites via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. Codango™ may also be linked to Web sites operated by companies affiliated with Codango. Visitors to those sites should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices.

Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Submissions

Should any visitor to Codango™ Web sites provide information, questions, comments, suggestions, reviews or any material through the feedback mechanisms located in the Web site, Codango™ shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information and shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute the information to others without limitation. The information expressed in any Reviews, Message Boards or chat rooms, or other forums conducted on Codango™, if any, are not necessarily those of Codango™ or its affiliated or related entities or content providers and Codango™ makes no representations or warranties regarding that information or those opinions.

Codango™ Market

Codango™ has released a utility that allows web site visitors to search for technology companies, for whatever purposes: be they career, business, or other research purposes. Should you decide to add your organization to the Codango™ Market, your consent to share your submitted contact information with other Codango™ Market visitors and buyers of the Codango™ Market list is implied. This utility is designed for legitimate business uses only.
